<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SeatSuite</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_guest">Edit Guest</string>
    <string name="title_activity_seat_guests">Seat Guests</string>

    <string-array name="Algorithms">
        <item>Bidding Based Seating</item>
        <item>Basic Seating</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>

    <string name="about">
        Hosting an event? \n
        Have picky guests and cannot figure out how to seat them? \n
        <i>No problem!</i> \n\n
        Seat Suite uses advanced algorithms to keep all of your guests happy.\n\n
        Just add your guests, set their seating preferences, and click go!\n\n
        It is that simple. The perfect seating arrangement is generated just for your event.\n
        An event with just fourteen guests has over 87 BILLION possible seating arrangements.\n

        So drop the pen and paper and let Seat Suite do all of the work for you! \n\n
        In just five minutes you will have the perfect seating plan so you can focus on having fun at your party.\n\n
        But don\'t just take our word for it- try it out and see for yourself! \n
        Happy guests make happy hosts, so here\'s to a great party, thrown by you!\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>

    <string name="helpTitle"><u>Help</u></string>
    <string name="helpWelcome">Welcome to Seat Suite. Lets help you get started!</string>

    <string name="helpTitle1"><u>Guest List:</u></string>
    <string name="help1sub">Here is where you can view all the guests you\'ve added </string>
    <string name="help1_1">- To add a guest, tap the + icon at the top right.</string>
    <string name="help1_2">- To delete a guest, slide their name left and tap delete.</string>
    <string name="help1_3">- To edit a guest, tap their name</string>
    <string name="help1_4">- To delete <i>all</i> guests, tap the trash icon on the toolbar</string>

    <string name="helpTitle2"><u>Add/Edit Guest:</u></string>
    <string name="help2sub">Here is where you can add a new guest, or edit an existing one </string>
    <string name="help2_1">- Set the user\'s name and age in the provided fields</string>
    <string name="help2_2">- Tip: After setting your guests age, try using the <i>auto-generate preferences feature</i> at the top right of the preference list</string>
    <string name="help2_3">- Move the sliders to set your guest\'s preferences</string>
    <string name="help2_4">- Tip: The red symbol will ensure guest A won\'t sit next to guest B</string>
    <string name="help2_5">- Tip: The star will ensure guest A <i>will</i> sit next to guest B</string>

    <string name="helpTitle3"><u>Seat Guests:</u></string>
    <string name="help3sub">Here is where the magic happens! Let\'s seat your guests </string>
    <string name="help3_1">- Simply tap <i>Go!</i> to generate the perfect seating arrangement</string>
    <string name="help3_2">- OR you can tap a seat to set who should sit there. Set as many as you want, then tap <i>Go!</i> </string>
    <string name="help3_3">- You can clear your selection by tapping the <i>Clear</i> button (same as go)</string>
    <string name="help3_4">- Tapping a seatted guest will tell you how happy they are with their neighbors, on a scale of 0 to 20</string>

    <string name="helpLuck">Good Luck and enjoy the party!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_testing">TestingActivity</string>


</resources>
